export default data3 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "What was the last battle between Great Britain and France?",
        options: ["The Battle of Trafalgar", "The Battle of Waterloo", "The Battle of Hastings", "Battle of Agincourt"],
        correct_option: "The Battle of Waterloo"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Which flower is associated with Wales?",
        options: ["Daffodil", "Rose", "Shamrock", "Thistle"],
        correct_option: "Daffodil"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "During the reign of Charles II parts of London were destroyed, what was the cause of this destruction?",
        options: ["A war", "A flood", "A fire", "An earthquake"],
        correct_option: "A fire"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "What charity works to preserve important buildings, coastline and countryside in the UK?",
        options: ["Shelter", "Age UK", "Crisis", "The National Trust"],
        correct_option: "The National Trust"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "Great Britain refers only to England, Wales and Scotland.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Who was the tribal leader who fought against the Romans?",
        options: ["Cleopatra", "Claudia", "Boudicca", "St Augustine"],
        correct_option: "Boudicca"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Who was voted the greatest Briton of all time in 2002?",
        options: ["Isaac Newton", "Winston Churchill", "Alexander Fleming", "Mo Farat"],
        correct_option: "Winston Churchill"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "When did women get the right to vote at the same age as men?",
        options: ["1918", "1928", "1938", "1948"],
        correct_option: "1928"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "Who is the head of the Church of England?",
        options: ["The Prime Minister", "The Archbishop of Canterbury", "The Pope", "The monarch"],
        correct_option: "The monarch"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "What sort of event is the Grand National?",
        options: ["Rugby", "Golf", "Horse Racing", "Tennis"],
        correct_option: "Horse Racing"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "What type of literature are the Canterbury Tales?",
        options: ["Poems", "Novels", "Jokes", "Fables"],
        correct_option: "Poems"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "When is Christmas Day?",
        options: ["24th of December", "25th of December", "26th of December", "27th of December"],
        correct_option: "25th of December"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "Who supported King Charles I during the Civil War?",
        options: ["Roundheads", "Suffragettes", "Quakers", "Cavaliers"],
        correct_option: "Cavaliers"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "What battle is commemorated in the Bayeux Tapestry?",
        options: ["The Battle of Waterloo", "The Battle of Trafalgar", "The Battle of Hastings", " The Battle of Britain"],
        correct_option: "The Battle of Hastings"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Where was Anne Boleyn, the wife of Henry VIII, executed?",
        options: [" Houses of the Parliament", "Stonehenge", "Tower of London", "Whitehall"],
        correct_option: "Tower of London"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Racial crime and smoking in public places are examples of:",
        options: ["Civil offences", "Criminal offences"],
        correct_option: "Criminal offences"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "What type of character was played by Charlie Chaplin?",
        options: ["A superhero", "A tramp", "A scientific genius", "A bandit"],
        correct_option: "A tramp"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Who developed the radar?",
        options: ["John Logie Baird", "Sir Frank Whittle", "Sir Christopher Cockrell", "Sir Robert Watson-Watt"],
        correct_option: "Sir Robert Watson-Watt"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Where is the official home of the Prime Minister?",
        options: ["18 Oxford Street", "Buckingham Palace", "Windsor Castle", "10 Downing Street"],
        correct_option: "10 Downing Street"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "Who is the author of the famous play ‘Macbeth’?",
        options: ["Alexander Thomas", "William Shakespeare", "Harold Pinter", "Evelyn Waugh"],
        correct_option: "William Shakespeare"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "What animal was cloned by scientists Sir Ian Wilmot and Keith Campbell?",
        options: ["A cow", "A rabbit", "A cat", "A sheep"],
        correct_option: "A sheep"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "What is the name of the building where the Northern Ireland Assembly meet?",
        options: ["Westminster", "Holyrood", "Senedd", "Stormont"],
        correct_option: "Stormont"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a World Heritage Site?",
        options: ["The London Eye", "Stonehenge", "The forts of Housesteads and Vindolanda", "The Houses of Parliament"],
        correct_option: "The London Eye"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "When was the Giant’s Causeway formed?",
        options: ["20 million years ago", "40 million years ago", "50 million years ago", "15 million years ago"],
        correct_option: "50 million years ago"
    }
]